[Music]
[Música]
You forgot to put what Nimu did yesterday before
te faltó poner lo de ayer de nimu antes
seeing Raed, what uh, everything came
de ver a raed el qué eh todo venía en
from the insecurity that I had,
base a la inseguridad que yo tenía u
but this, what is this? Last night he
Pero esto Qué es anoche lugar anoche se
started doing a live stream talking about
puso a hacer un directo hablando de
Dallas, what did I say? No, what I said, neither
Dallas que dije no esto que dije tampoco
a kiss, Mik, last night he put on
un beso mik anoche se puso en
a live stream on Christmas Eve talking about
nochebuenas ha un directo hablando de
Dallas. Oh, to fall for it, she was really stupid, bad
Dallas Ay para caer era re estúpida mal
vibes, yes, I can assure you with 100%
onda sí puedo asegurar con 100% de
veracity that I am a
veracidad de que soy una persona
very different person, Wismi, you still
bastante diferente wismi te sigue
think I'm God. Let's see, you didn't insult, but
pareciendo God a ver no insultaste pero
you asked a question that, if I
hiciste una pregunta que puede si es que
answer it one way or another,
la contesto de cierta u otra manera
could get me into one. Kiss. ​​Hey,
puede meterme en una un beso Oye
we're 26. We're already more than
llevamos 26 Eh ya llevamos más de la
halfway through controversy, I mean, you're clearly
mitad polémica o sea claramente estás
looking for something interesting. And although I could give an
buscando chicha Y aunque podría dar una
answer that doesn't bother anyone, I'm not
respuesta que no moleste a nadie no te
going to give it to you just because you
la voy a dar solamente por el hecho que
're looking for controversy, I'm seeing your
estás buscando polémica estoy viendo tus
ulterior motives. So no, I'm not going
dobles intenciones Entonces no no te voy
to answer you, but just so I don't give you
a contestar pero solamente para no darte
the pleasure. I saw how people were looking at you
el gusto yo vi cómo gente te miraba
before, it turned out when you updated, it's
antes se volvió cuando actualizaste es
the Avatar, I don't know the truth, there are many.  there are
el Avatar no sé la verdad hay muchas hay
many reasons why people got a crush on me
muchas razones por las que la gente me
and they still get a crush on me
agarró Manía y me sigue agarrando Manía
today eh cheer up For nothing, for nothing
el día de hoy eh nimo Por nada por nada
cheer up I don't understand why it's very
animo No entiendo el Por qué es muy
complex the truth is it's a subject of
complejo la verdad es un tema de
complex sociology and I, I know that
sociología compleja e yo yo sé que no
I'm not everyone's cup of tea
soy plato de buen gusto para todo el
eh And that's what I'm happy with I mean it was
mundo eh Y con eso me conformo o sea era
something that before I couldn't get over like
algo que antes yo no podía superar tipo
I said why are there people who don't like me at
Yo decía por qué hay gente que no le
all no idea why and now it
caigo bien nada ni idea Por qué y ahora
's like I don't give a damn and I
es como me la me la sopla y me la
snort at him completely like I think it
resopla rotundamente onda Yo creo que
was also because of the lack of self-love
también era por la falta de amor propio
that I wanted them to love me like love me
que quería que me amen tipo ámenme
because I don't love myself eh the
porque no me amo a mí misma eh las
famous deficiencies that we talk about
famosas carencias de las que hablamos
many times that make us look for
muchas veces que hacen que busquemos las
solutions in places where they don't
soluciones en lugares donde no
correspond instead of within ourselves
corresponde en vez de nuestro interior
I hope that Gan that judgment against has to
Espero que Gan ese juicio contra ha de
receive what he deserves no I can't say
recibir su merecido no no puedo decir
anything because I'm in the middle of that but don't
nada porque estoy en medio de eso pero
worry everything is fine Delox in fact
tranquilo está todo Bueno delox de hecho
put a Claro Look I'm going to tell you one
puso un Claro Mira os voy a decir una
thing I'm going to tell you one thing but it is that
cosa os voy a decir una cosa pero es que
I can be wrong but well
es que me puedo equivocar pero bueno
like delos  has made something
como delos ha puesto en público una cosa
luar public Please give me the link to
luar Me pones porfi el link del del
delo's Twitter please so as not to leak
Twitter de delo porfi para no filtrar Yo
anything I'm not doing anything but you know the impression
nada e pero a mí sabéis la impresión que
I get that they haven't sued a [ __ ]
me da de que no han demandado una [__]
thing the impression I get is
[__] a mí la impresión que me dan es
that they haven't sued a [ __ ] thing they have
que no han demandado una [__] [__] han
sent a burofax asking Dallas to back
mandado un burofax pidiéndole a Dallas
down what Luis gendera did to me a
que se retr lo que me hizo el Luis
kiss Luis Look paripe nimu is
gendera un beso Luis Mira paripe nimu es
the least indicated to talk about
la menos indicada para hablar de
puppies Merry Christmas gorgeous Greetings
perritos Feliz Navidad guapísimo Saludos
from ribo two hearts two hearts
desde ribo dos corazones dos corazones
Halloween pumpkin oh my god
calabaza de Halloween madre mía el
delo's Twitter is from Dallas eh I mean
Twitter de delo es de Dallas eh o sea el
delox's Twitter is Look and with utbh they
Twitter de delox es Mira e con utbh que
have spoken because they have started to
se ha hablado porque se han puesto a
mess with Dallas a kiss I think
meterse con el Dallas un beso yo creo
utbh will not end up having a relationship
que utbh no acabará teniendo relación
with these people there will be a cordiality
con esta gento tendrá una cordialidad
but apart from that I mean I don't consider utbh
pero aparte o sea yo no considero utbh
I want to not consider him to be of the same
quiero no considerarlo de la misma
caliber as delo and Ricky he would
calaña que el delo y el Ricky me haría
disappoint me Maris a kiss By the way
una decepción a Maris un beso Por cierto
eh Even if he is bald gorgeous eh
eh Aunque este sea calvo guapísima eh
gorgeous that  she's gorgeous that's
guapisima que está guapísima que está la
utbh's girlfriend I don't know how much longer a
novia de utbh no sé cuánto le queda un
kiss Alex eh delox's Twitter It's
beso Alex eh el Twitter de delox Es
about Dallas eh Look miare posted
sobre Dallas eh Mira miare ha puesto
something about Dallas no well that the
algo de Dallas no bueno que los
Dallas followers have insulted him in
seguidores de Dallas le han insultado en
a message no later we'll see if maybe he
un mensaje no luego lo veremos si acaso
made an account that messes with pambi
hecho una cuenta que se mete con pambi
Merry Christmas this month I'm turning 5 hbre
Feliz Navidad este mes hago 5 aos hbre
handsome How are you a kiss supermark no no no
guapo Cómo estás un beso supermark no no
no she's here because she met her because she
no no esta porque la conoció porque la
met her here debating with me and she's a
conoció aquí debatiendo conmigo y es
dala hater the chick and this is about pambi
hater de dala la tipa e esto sobre pambi
31,000 likes this tweet from nimus come on
31.000 likes este tweet de nimus vamos
I don't believe that or vina a kiss
eso no me lo creo yo ni vina un beso
31,000 likes eh this tweet from nimus no
31.000 likes eh este tweet de nimus ni
way your channel It's about Dallas No
de coña tu canal Es sobre Dallas No
man my channel what the [ __ ] is it going to be about
hombre mi canal qué [__] va a ser sobre
Dallas my channel Today he's talking about
Dallas mi canal Hoy está hablando de
Dallas because nimu and delo started
Dallas porque nimu y delo se han puesto
talking about Dallas yes nimu and delo don't
a hablar de Dallas si nimu y delo no
talk about Dallas I don't know not even here we
hablan de Dallas yo no sé ni aquí que
talk about Dallas yes Dallas right now
hablamos de Dallas si Dallas ahora mismo
wasn't involved in any thing or anything like that
no estaba metido en ninguna cosa ni nada
But well what was it Ah yes
por el estilo Pero bueno e qué era Ah sí
yes yes I know what I wanted to see but I haven't
sí sí ya sé lo que quería yo ver pero no
seen it he deleted it 32,000 likes
lo he visto lo ha borrado 32,000 likes
this doesn't have a damn thing Look if
esto es que no tiene ni de coña Mira si
my exclusive about Hari's divorce on Twitter had 12,000 112,000 likes
12000 112000 likes tuvo en Twitter mi
Juan and
exclusiva del divorcio de hari Juan y me
these people are trying to tell me that the
están queriendo decir esta gente que el
fake review of Animu has the same thing What
fake review de animu tiene lo mismo Qué
tweet was it he deleted it luar it was a tweet
tet fue lo ha borrado luar era un twet
where it said something about Dallas pick up the
donde decía algo de Dallas recoge los
burofax pick up the burofax exactly it has
burofax recoge los burofax exactamente
more likes it has more likes the
tiene más likes tiene más likes los
tweets that you visit the podcast I find it
tweets que visitas el podcast yo lo veo
weird but oh well I don't know maybe it's that
rarete pero bueno no lo sé a lo mejor es
on Twitter a lot of his
que en Twitter se recomiendan muchos sus
tweets are recommended dude there was a tweet that said
tweets tío había un tweet que él decía
Dallas pick up the burofax This look birmar
Dallas coge los burofax Este mira birmar
deleted pambi last week I
ha eliminado pambi la semana pasada me
met with the ceo of bmar and I took the opportunity
reuní con el ceo de bmar y aproveché
to explain to him what happened with pambi v
para exponerle lo ocurrido con pambi v
that you imagine this guy talking about
que tú imagínate a este tío hablando de
pambi everywhere by the way Daniel
pambi en todas partes por cierto Daniel
less threesomes Why less threesomes Why
menos tríos Por qué menos tríos Por qué
Alex a kiss and more pick up the burofax of
Alex un beso y más [__] los burofax de
what  are you scared, midon, I mean, and more so picking up
qué tienes miedo midón o sea y más [__]
the burofaxes if you file a lawsuit, you do
los burofax si tú pones una demanda tú
n't, you don't send a burofax, so what I get
no tú no mandas un burofax entonces a mí
the impression is that these
lo que me da la impresión es de que esta
people will be trying to send
gente le andarán intentando mandar
burofaxes to Dallas, those burofaxes of the
burofax a Dallas de esos burofax del
kind if you don't apologize, we'll file a
palo si no pides Perdón te ponemos una
lawsuit, eh. It seems to me
demanda eh A mí me da la impresión de
that What is that, eh? He hasn't filed a lawsuit that he's going to
que Qué es eso eh No ha demandado qu va
file a lawsuit in Dubai, it seems to me that that's
a poner una demanda en Dubai a mí me da
it, eh if he's
la impresión de que es eso eh si está
saying, Ah, pick up the burofaxes, it doesn't make
diciendo Ah recoge los burofax no tiene
sense. What happens if he gives the headquarters and
sentido Qué pasa si da la sede y pide
apologizes, eh. Let's see, I don't know what would
perdón eh A ver pues yo no sé lo que
happen regarding that issue of the
pasaría em respecto al tema ese de lo
dog, it's not what she wants to
del perro no es lo que ella quiere
sue, no, what Dallas told her about the
demandar no lo que le dijo Dallas de lo
dog, what her ex had told her is
del perro que le había dicho el ex es
that you know that it is, it's very subjective,
que ya sabéis que es es muy subjetivos
that what one judge tells you yes, another
que lo que un juez te dice que sí otro
tells you no. So I don't know what would
te dice no Entonces no lo sé lo que
happen, the first thing is for the
pasaría lo primero es que le llegue la
lawsuit to reach her, the first thing is for her to sue
demanda lo primero es que la lo demande
in Dubai. Of course, sue in Dubai and and and that it
en Dubai Claro que lo demande en Dubai y
has a path in Dubai  Of
y que y que tenga recorrido en Dubai
course,
claro se tiene que valorar el e se tiene
the things that Nimu says about
que valorar las cosas que nimu dice de
him have to be valued, too, not insults that have been
él también no insultos que se hayan
said to each other and
dicho mutuamente y se tendrá que valorar
the veracity or not of what I don't know has to be valued.
la veracidad o no de lo que no sé se
Every man has to be valued. Let's see, it's
tiene que valorar todo hombre a ver es
one thing to tell someone that you
una cosa lo de decirle a alguien que te
sleep with dogs, not that you [ __ ]
acuestas con perros no que te follas a
a dog or that or that you have slept with a dog. He did
un perro o que o que te has acostado con
n't tell them No, that he slept
un perro no le dijo No que se acostaba
with a dog. Of course, that
con un perro no Claro eso evidentemente
is obviously actionable if you tell someone for
es demandable si se lo sueltas a alguien
free. Yes, it is worth it now in the
gratuitamente Sí vale ahora en el
context that they have of war,
contexto que ellos tienen de guerra
man. I believe that Nimu has shared
hombre Yo creo que nimu ha compartido
things where he calls the other a pedophile and
cosas donde al otro lo llama pedófilo y
things like that, that would be valued
cosas por el estilo ent eso se valoraría
if you are in a dispute with a
si tú estás en una contienda con una
person in which you are calling
persona en la que tú le estás diciendo a
one a pedophile and the other tells you that you are
uno pedófilo y el otro te dice que estás
sleeping with a dog. Well, I don't know what would
acostado con un perro Pues no sé yo qué
happen, you understand what I'm saying, I'm not a
pasaría me entiendes qué te digo no soy
fortune teller. Personally, if I am
adivino yo personalmente si le estoy
telling a person that he is a groomer
diciendo a una persona que es un groomer
and a scammer, well, I'm not going to sue him
y un estafador pues no lo voy a demandar
because the next day he tells me  son
porque al día siguiente él me diga hijo
of a [ __ ] or that I [ __ ] a goat What do you
de [__] o que me folo una cabra Qué
want me to tell you in the first place
quieres que te diga en primer lugar
because I would be a little ballsy
porque me estaría un poco los [__]
also I tell you eh perfect I am
también te digo eh perfecto estoy ahora
right now with that issue and no I don't know until
mismo con ese tema y no no sé hasta qu
I sue a person who continues
yo demando a una persona que sigue al
day to day, I mean, one thing is that you HM
día a día o sea una cosa es que tú HM
one thing is that you have had a
una cosa es que tú hayas tenido un
conflict with a person okay eh in
conflicto con una persona vale eh en el
2022 okay you in 2022 you have had a
2022 vale tú en el 2022 has tenido un
conflict with a person you have
conflicto con una persona os habéis
insulted each other okay if I sue
insultado mutuamente vale si yo demando
that person for the insults that he
a esa persona por los insultos que me
makes me in the days after that
haga los días posteriores a eso
obviously it is encouragement retor kandy no and they are
evidentemente es ánimo retor kandy no y
not going to condemn him Sure but man
no le van a condenar Claro pero hombre
if that person continues to insult you
si esa persona sigue insultándote
strongly during all the weeks of
fuertemente durante todas las seman del
2023 and during all the weeks of 2024
2023 y durante todas las seman del 2024
man then I think that
hombre pues ahí Creo que no le va a
what I told him in 2022 is not going to be valid eh I
valer lo que yo le haya dicho en 2022 eh
think eh I think but well there are people who
creo eh creo pero bueno hay personas que
believe that yes eh There are people who
se creen que sí eh Hay personas que se
believe that because I told you I don't know that in
creen que porque yo te dije no sé que en
2022 you  it's going to serve so that you, which
el 2022 te va a servir para que tú que
is a blank check for you to say whatever
es una carta blanca para que tú digas lo
you want in 2022, 2023, 2024
que tú quieras el 2022 el 2023 el 2024 y
and now we start on the 25th And of course it seems to
y ahora Empezamos el 25 Y claro me da a
me that no, it seems to me that no but
mí que no eh me da a mí que no pero
well, each one, each one does what they
bueno cada uno cada uno que que haga lo
can assume, period, I can
que lo que pueda asumir punto puedo
talk so not everything is fine with
hablar así que no está todo bien con
Dallas that the two of them came out to talk
Dallas que salieron a hablar los dos
together, wow, there are times when I say, hey,
juntos buah hay veces que digo Che todo
everyone found out about this, how bad or how
el mundo se enteró de esto qué mal o qué
good or whatever and I say there are no people
bien o lo que sea y y digo no hay gente
who live in a bubble or or or well or
que vive en una burbuja o o o bueno o
luckily they don't find out about things
por suerte no se entera de las cosas
because sometimes I say how envious of
porque yo a veces digo qué envidia de la
people How envious of people who don't
gente Qué envidia de la gente que no se
get into controversies or find out about
mete en polémicas ni se entera en
controversies or anything I mean today I
polémicas ni nada O sea a día de hoy Yo
am that person but I don't give a damn H all
soy esa persona pero me chupa H todas
the controversies eh but of course there are people who
las polémicas eh pero claro hay gente
are updated with the
que que que está resesa actualizada el
Lore I prefer to have my community people
Lore prefiero tener mi comunidad gente
who suck them off, blow them a dick, the
que le chupe le sople una [__] la la
controversy than who care because let's
polémica que que que le importe porque a
see both of them I'm going to  to accept those who
ver ambos los voy a aceptar a los que
ler also said that Javi did have
ler también dijo que Javi sí tenía
privileged information for the 10,000
información privilegiada por los 10,000
well nothing happens ler is going to deliver a
bueno no pasa nada ler va a entregar un
tweet of mine from 2022 it will surely
tweet mío del 2022 seguramente le le
turn out well he likes gossip and those
salga bien le gusta el salseo y a los
who don't but eh I mean even if it doesn't seem like it to
que no pero eh o sea aunque no parezca a
me I hate gossip both that of
mí yo odio el salseo tanto el de los
others and that I win it Ah or or me
demás como que me lo Gan a mí Ah o o yo
being in the middle of gossip because it's
estar en medio de un salseo porque es
horrible it's horrible and on the other hand I'm
horrible es horrible y por otro lado A
not interested in the lives of other
mí no me interesa la vida de las demás
people I mean no you you you We have 30 out of
personas o sea no tu tu tú Tenemos 30 de
50 eh how good the people who don't get
50 eh qué bien la gente que no se mete
into controversy proceed to delete it twi Javi
en polémica procede a borrarle twi Javi
No no yes count this crack What do I
No no sí cuent esta crack A mí que me
care about the controversy of the reborn with a cat
importa la polémica del reborn con gata
with auron Play that I don't know what happened to him with
con auron Play que no sé qué le pasó con
b I don't give a damn and half of the other what do
b me chupa un huevo y la mitad del otro
people do with their lives I mean
que hace la gente con sus vidas o sea
turn off the Radio Amigo one thing that really pisses
apagada la Radio Amigo yo una cosa que
me off is that for example
me da mucha bronca es que por ejemplo
someone asks in a comment says
alguien pregunta en un comentario pone
Why was it a nana nimu or why  what are you
Por qué fue unana nimu o por qué están
so angry with nimu or why I don't know
tan enojados con nimu o por qué no sé
what about nimu and there's always that guy I quote
qué de nimu y Nunca falta el chavon cito
who says some of these things because he
que dice alguna de estas cosas porque
's F a lot of people Oh Because he ruined his
está F mucha gente Oh Porque arruinó la
career Alex 31 19 super chat and I'll put
carrera Alex 31 19 super chat y os pongo
an audio it would be the first and only audio
un audio sería el primer y único audio
that I'm going to advance of the rewine eh if we
que voy a adelantar del rewine eh si
arrive eh that I still have my doubts
llegamos eh que todavía tengo mis dudas
eh it was from many vtubers or he committed
eh era de muchísimas vtubers o cometió
war crimes or in his life he
crímenes de guerra o en su vida pasar
was Hitler no I mean There's always someone who's
era Hitler no O sea Nunca falta uno que
going to misinform with lies So
va a desinformar con mentiras Entonces
that bothered me a lot because I said I
eso me molestaba mucho porque decía yo
said hey crazy they're going to lie
decía va loco van a mentir
blatantly with all those things and I
descaradamente con todas esas cosas y yo
can't do anything because if I
no puedo hacer nada porque si le
answer him I'm giving him attention ah eh
contesto le estoy dando atención ah eh
if I answer him I'm giving attention Ah and
si le contesto estoy dando atención Ah y
he's trying to take down my
está tir intentando tirarme la cuenta de
Twitter account there are surely videos already of
Twitter seguro que hay vídeos ya de
people talking about that I mean come on I'm
gente hablando de eso o sea es que vamos
risking my neck come on of course Javi
me juego el cuello vamos claro Javi
oliveira this guy is an [ __ ] tesa What's up
oliveira este tío es [__] tesa Qué
sweetheart this guy is an [ __ ] eh
pasa corazón este tío es [__] eh
Javi oliveira that position as censor
Javi oliveira ese puesto como censurador
and puts here again  These are the [ __ ] bad accounts
y pone aquí otra vez las cuentas malitas
saying that
estas de los [__] [__] diciendo que
I've knocked down that I haven't knocked down a
yo he tumbado que yo no he tumbado una
[ __ ] thing that I don't knock anything down but
[__] [__] que yo no tumbo nada pero
how am I going to knock anything down that I never
que yo como voy a tumb nada que yo no
throw anything away dude really This is a
tiro nada nunca tío de verdad Este es un
[ __ ] [ __ ] with three pairs of
[__] [__] de de tres pares de
balls eh Let's see dad this one is an idiot
[__] eh A ver pap este que es idiota
dude Why the [ __ ] am I going to throw if I don't
tío Para qué [__] voy a tirar si yo no
want them to stop talking about me there's no way there
quiero que paren de hablar de mí es que
's no worse idea than to make sure that
no hay no hay peor idea que ponerte a
nobody talks about me that this one doesn't
que no hablen de mí nadie que este no
talk about me that the other one doesn't mention me
hable de mí que el otro no me mencione
anymore Alex a kiss Many millions is your
más Alex un beso Muchas millos es tu
name but of course people
nombre pero por supuesto que la gente
understood that I don't know why he never
entendió que yo no sé por qué n le llegó
spoke to Javi leir on some
a hablar a Javi leir en alguna
occasion why Because even
oportunidad por qué Porque incluso antes
before Dala messed with Nimu Javi
de que dala se metiera con nimu Javi ya
already messed with Nimu he was angry with him he was
antes se metía con nimu le tenía rabia
angry with him So I don't know he
le tenía cólera Entonces no sé lo
forgave him and that's it but well it was like it was
perdonó y ya pero bueno como que se
known that this Oh really if it is that already
sabía que esto Ay de verdad si es que ya
a kiss jaile how are you Thank you very much now
un beso jaile qué tal Muchísimas gracias
visible what he's going to say dude
visible ya lo que va a decir tío
for free when  you're going to see it well you're
gratuitamente cuando lo va a ver bien lo
going to see it [ __ ] great that it has knocked me down
va a ver de [__] madre que me ha tumbado
Look, it causes the result thing I
los Mira provoque el resultado cosa yo
also criticize people who post
también critico a las personas que ponen
tweets and then take a picture or back out
tweets y luego se retratan o se echan
and end up deleting their tweet, I
para atrás y terminan borrando su tweet
mean, I don't know why they do it, the
o sea no sé para qué lo hacen yo las
only times I've deleted a tweet has
únicas veces que he borrado tweet ha
been when I had
sido cuando he tenido faltas
spelling mistakes car tan meme badly stated
ortográficas car tan meme enunciado mal
So nothing more but these people
Entonces nada más pero que esta gente lo
do it all the time Juan guarnizo
hace a cada rato Juan guarnizo la madre
auron's mother Play now nimu too Well
de auron Play ahora nimu también Bueno
let's see what tweet he put people
vamos a ver qué twet le puso gente lo
see it so that Javi Oliveira himself can
vea como para que el mismo Javi oliveira
see it in that case you would have written
lo vea en tal caso le hubieses escrito
to him privately Although Javi might have
al privado Aunque igual Javi lo hubiese
leaked it too Ah Why are you deleting it
filtrado también Ah Para qué lo borras
now here is this what the peñita says
ya aquí está esto qué dice la peñita
came to clarify a clip where they pointed out
vino a matizar un clip donde señalaban a
Dallas as bullying more B who invents
Dallas de bullying má B que inventa
five the death of Serene is channel
cinco la muerte de serene se canal
deleted by thumbnails seven
borrado por miniaturas siete
collaborations with puppies at the moment
colaboraciones con perritos de momento
I'm in the fridge it deserves a video
voy en el frigor se merece ya un video
in my image a few euros it seems
en mi imagen unos eurillos que parece
that things are bad in the
que está la cosa chunga en el
fridge  because of my clip Merry
frigorífico por culpa de mi clip Feliz
Christmas this user is re-uploading my
Navidad este usuario está resubiendo mi
content adding their own
contenido agregándole su propia marca de
watermark and profiting at the expense of my image
agua y lucr a Costa de mi imagen
affecting the monetization of my
afectando a la monetización de mi
content gone partially summarize it on
contenido ido resumirlo parcialmente en
another platform Well at least he didn't say you
otra plataforma Bueno al menos no dijo
were watching a
que estabas mirando una película de
Marvel movie no [ __ ] he is an [ __ ] dude he has to
Marvel no [__] es [__] tío
shoehorn in Okay but
tiene que meter por calzador Bueno pero
Dallas but Dallas when I was in
Dallas pero Dallas yo cuánd estaba a
favor of Dallas throwing I don't know what I don't know
favor de que Dallas tire no sé qué no sé
how much and I'm an [ __ ] but the thing is that he has to
cuánto y yo [__] pero es que él
please that he has to
tiene que agradar a eso él tiene que
then eh How did I let that stop
entonces eh Cómo deje que eso me deje de
bothering me for the simple fact of what
molestar por el simple hecho de lo que
you but see I don't throw out [ __ ] [ __ ]
vos pero ve Yo no tiro una [__] [__]
Look at this this is a channel dedicated to me
Mira este esto es un canal dedicado a mí
this is a channel where I post a
esto es un canal de que yo pongo un
tweet and there's a video of that tweet okay
tweet y hay un vídeo de ese tweet vale
eh what am I going to throw out let me put whatever I
eh queé voy a tirar yo que ponga lo que
want put whatever I want mm nice
quiera que ponga lo que quiera mm buenas
tits Dalas m javio oliveira makes his
tetitas Dalas m javio oliveira hace su
own Hispanic rigu and here he will surely
propio rigu hispano y aquí seguramente
have said Ah well well you were messing
habrá dicho Ah pues pues tú te metías
with Alex cool I don't know what he has to
con Alex molón no sé que tiene que
please you know if he doesn't even know
agradar sabes si es que no sabe ni
the  times that I've seen it is
siquiera e las veces que lo he visto es
that he doesn't even have an opinion because
que ni siquiera tiene una opinión porque
no no he doesn't know what to think Because if he does have an opinion it
no no no sabe qué opinar Porque si opina
may contradict what he thought
a puede que se contradiga con el día
yesterday Well anyway what Omar just said
anterior bueno en fin un acaba de decir
Because if the kid who asked
Omar Porque si el pibe que preguntó por
why it was an nimu goes to reality and
qué fue un an nimu va a la realidad y
contrasts the information that they're
contrasta esa información que le están
giving him, that is to say the guy goes to Google and
dando es decir el chavón va a Google y
searches and finds out well about me that's what
busca y Averigua bien sobre mí que eso
a person with criteria would do, a
haría una persona con criterio una
person with common sense would grab and
persona con sentido común agarraría y
look this up it's true Oh it was a lie I do
buscaría esto es verdad Oh era mentira
n't know what I don't know how much and contrast it you
no sé qué no sé cuánto y lo contrastar
know what I mean it would be a person that I
me entendés sería una persona que yo
would love in my community but if that
quisiera mi comunidad pero si esa
person stays with a
persona se queda con un comentario
stupid comment from someone who is
estúpido de alguien que le está
deliberately lying to him and it's a
mintiendo deliberadamente y es un
phone it's composed with it It's a
teléfono es compuesto con ello Es una
person that I'm interested in in my community
persona que me interese en mi comunidad
anyway because he doesn't even have
de todas maneras porque no tiene ni
a minimum of common sense to
siquiera un mínimo de sentido común como
look for the information on his own
para buscar la información por su cuenta
So at that moment it stopped
Entonces en ese momento me dejó de
bothering me, it stopped bothering me that they
molestar sea me dejó de molestar que
lie so much about me that people believe it
tanto que mientan sobre mí que la gente
Because both those who lie
se lo crea Porque tanto los que mienten
and those who believe it are of the
como los que se lo creen están en la
same ilk, I mean they're people who don't
misma calaña o sea son gente que no Se
inform themselves  and and it sucks just for the sake of it but you know
informa y y que jode por [__] pero saes
the worst thing is that these rumors are
que lo peor que estos rumores los
spread by people who don't have followers
difunde gente que no tiene seguidores
like what is Pepito
igual qué Qué es Pepito
with TR followers and he goes and says he scammed I don't
con TR seguidores y va y dice estafó no
know what bro you know that there's something
sé qué bro vos sabes que est hay algo
more important places like this it
más importante lugares de esto es que me
gives me a little bit of pere anmo the truth is that it's
da un poco de pere anmo la verdad que es
like this no no it's not that I've already
como esto ya no no es que esto ya lo
experienced this it's that nmo it's like he gets
viví es que nmo es como que se raya
really carried away with things he gives things a lot of thought
mucho con las cosas le da muchas vueltas
you know it's done it's done a lot
a las cosas sabes se hace se hace mucho
with stories you know It gets really carried away
con las historias sabes Se raya mucho
with you spending Christmas Eve trying to
con tú echarte la Nochebuena intentando
take down Javi Oliveira's Twitter account
tirarle la cuenta de Twitter a Javi
fore
oliveira fore
[Music]
[Música]